[Music]
[音乐]
all right well welcome to my session my
好的，欢迎参加我的会议
name is Allegra Kowski I work for
我叫Allegra Kowski
pivotal this is my second time at the
关键，这是我第二次
spring i/o last year and second time in
去年春季I / O，第二次在
Brussels on it for that matter beautiful
布鲁塞尔就此事美丽
city so quickly about myself
这么快就我自己的城市
I'm originally from Ukraine moved to the
我原来是从乌克兰搬到
United States around 90s lived there for
90年代左右的美国在那里居住
a little bit and then last year moved to
一点点，然后去年搬到
France so I'm kind of just across the
法国，所以我有点像
border
边界
my history with spring organization is
我在春季组织的历史是
interesting I joined spring source in
有趣的是我加入了Spring Source
2008 worked my way up to engineering on
2008年一直致力于工程设计
spring integration by the way we're
通过我们的方式实现 Spring Integration
gonna be talking a lot about it today or
今天要谈论很多，或者
touching on it how many of you familiar
谈到它，你们中有多少人熟悉
with spring integration framework all
与spring集成框架一起
right good
对的好
so I work as an engineer on spring
所以我在春季当工程师
integration framework and then around
整合框架，然后围绕
2012 I decided to guys will remember the
2012年，我决定让大家记住
Hadoop big data that buzz word so I
Hadoop大数据让我措手不及
decided to try my myself in that area we
决定在那个地区尝试我自己
went to work for a company called
去一家叫公司的公司工作
Hortonworks
霍顿工厂
which is now cloud era and a few years
现在是云时代和几年
ago decided that's really not my cup of
以前认为那真的不是我的那杯
tea and decided to came back come back
茶，决定回来回来
to spring team rejoined and was we have
The Spring Team 重新加入，我们有
this interesting role which is kind of
这个有趣的角色
important for you guys we have any role
对你们很重要，我们有任何作用
called spring advisory architects which
叫做春季咨询建筑师
are the actual engineers were also visit
实际的工程师也都来了吗
the field so they're committers on
领域，所以他们是提交者
variety of different frameworks and so
各种不同的框架等等
when if you whatever business dealings
什么时候进行业务交易
you have with pivotal industry
你在关键行业
organization you may want to know about
您可能想了解的组织
that that we do have that it's so it's
我们确实有这样的事实
not like your regular consultant is
不像您的定期顾问
sexual spring engineer who also visits
性春天工程师，他还会去
the clients so I did that for about six
客户，所以我做了大约六个
months until
几个月前
the guy who was leading sprinkles team
领导者撒队
decided to leave and they were looking
决定离开，他们正在寻找
for somebody to take the leadership of
让某人去领导
the framework so they offered me I took
框架，所以他们为我提供了
it and then later on the same happened
它，然后后来发生了同样的事情
with a spring court function so I
具有春季法院职能，所以我
currently lead to project strength of
目前导致项目实力
streaming sprinkles function so and what
流洒功能如何
that's what we're going to be talking
这就是我们要谈论的
about today also just as far as the
大约今天也一样
protocol I prefer not to wait till the
协议我不想等到
very end for questions so I'll
问题的结局很深，所以我会
periodically stop I'll say if anybody
定期停止我会说如果有人
has any questions please do so because I
有任何问题请这样做，因为我
believe the question is more relevant
相信这个问题更相关
when it's asked within context of what
在什么情况下被问到
just being presented rather than wait
只是被呈现而不是等待
till the end and so on but if for
直到最后等等，但是如果
example you kind of jumping ahead I'm
例如，你有点向前迈
going to say hold up I'm gonna talk
会说要坚持，我要说
about it and so on so let's begin here's
关于它等等，让我们开始这里
our kind of Amenia agenda I only have a
我们的Amenia议程只有一个
few slides for those of you who know me
一些认识我的人的幻灯片
I spend most of my time just live coding
我大部分时间都花在现场编码上
so that's what I'm going to do today but
所以这就是我今天要做的
I set the context with a few slides so
我用几张幻灯片设置了背景
we're gonna talk about cloud
我们要谈论云
event-driven architecture kind of bring
事件驱动架构带来的
everything together we're gonna talk
我们一起谈论的一切
about what's primarily what's new what's
关于主要是什么
come what's what's coming what's new in
来是什么，来了，新来了
spring clouds streaming what's coming in
春天的云流进来了什么
a pipeline so cloud we live in the
管道，使我们生活在云中
industry full of buzzwords right so
行业充满流行语吧
today we have cloud rewind 10 years ago
今天我们有云倒带10年前
we had SOA and then we can remind
我们有SOA，然后我们可以提醒
another 10 years and probably come up
再过十年，可能还会来
with some other buzzwords but there is
还有一些其他流行词，但有
why I'm kind of making sarcastic comment
为什么我有点讽刺评论
about this is because there is no
关于这是因为没有
definition of what SOA is there's no
没有什么SOA的定义
definition of what cloud is everybody
每个人都对云的定义
perceives it the way it is relevant to
以与之相关的方式感知它
them so so when when I talk about cloud
所以当我谈论云时
I at least want to set the context what
我至少想设置上下文
it means to me right so cloud is an
对我来说，这意味着云是
ecosystem that integrates platforms in
整合平台的生态系统
the middleware into one cohesive hybrid
中间件成为一个内聚的混合体
runtime right so we have we outsourcing
运行时正确，所以我们将外包
infrastructure we
基础设施我们
sourcing variety of different
采购品种不同
connectivity and business processes to
连接和业务流程
to the cloud because we are the
到云，因为我们是
developers we primarily want to
我们主要想要的开发人员
concentrate on implementing functional
专心执行功能
requirements and don't want to bother
要求，不想打扰
with the sort of a boilerplate nature of
具有某种样板性质
today's IT environments and for those of
当今的IT环境以及
you who've been with spring for a while
你已经和春天在一起了一段时间
you know that's really our message
你知道那真的是我们的信息
that's that's our that's the historical
那就是我们那就是历史
message that we always had we worry
消息，我们总是有我们担心
about the boilerplate code leaving you
关于样板代码离开你
only with the functional concerns so
仅在功能方面如此
events so this talk this session is
事件，因此本次会议的讨论是
primarily about talking about
主要是谈论
event-driven architectures and my goal
事件驱动的架构和我的目标
is actually as a lead of both projects
实际上是两个项目的牵头人
to primarily showcase the kind of a
主要展示一种
nitty-gritty technical aspects what can
实质性技术方面可以做什么
you do with the framework necessarily
您必须使用框架
deviate into how what what are the
偏离了什么是什么
practical implications of it in fact
实际上它的实际含义
jakob Gilliam on one of my colleagues
jakob Gilliam对我的一位同事
who's gonna be presenting right after
谁会在之后出现
this he is a big advocate of
这是他的大力倡导者
event-driven architectures he has a lot
他有很多事件驱动的架构
of practical demos and presentations and
实用演示和演示文稿以及
so on because he is a developer advocate
之所以这样，是因为他是开发者的拥护者
he visits the field he does this cool
他去现场，他做的很酷
stuff so in other words it's a kind of a
东西，换句话说，这是一种
nice transition to know what's in what's
很好的过渡，以了解什么是什么
internally going on how things work
在内部研究事物的运作方式
together and then you know see how it
在一起，然后你知道如何
actually works in practice so um so
实际上在实践中起作用
events what is event events is a
事件是事件，事件是
representation of state change so when
状态变化的表示，所以什么时候
you receive event what's in the event
您收到事件事件
already happened it's always in the past
已经发生了，它总是过去
tense
紧张
right so the events are delivered in the
正确，因此事件在
sort of form the protocol specific
某种形式的协议专用
messages and be a variety of different
消息和各种不同
middleware so we can have you know
中间件，这样我们就可以知道
messaging systems HTTP I mean you can
邮件系统HTTP我的意思是你可以
argue that literally anything that can
争辩说，实际上任何可以
transmit piece of information is a
传输一条信息是
messaging middle-way
消息传递中途
so not necessarily has to be like JMS or
因此不一定必须像JMS或
MVP or Kafka or anything else so there
MVP或Kafka或其他任何东西
is something about event and why is it
是关于事件的，为什么呢
why we kind of come up with a different
为什么我们会提出不同的建议
name rather than just piece of data
名称而不只是数据
because events to me at least means that
因为发生在我身上的事件至少意味着
there is going to be a piece of
会有一块
information and there's going to be a
信息，将会有一个
piece of meta information right so in
一条元信息就这样
other words just like with the email
就像电子邮件一样
just like with a regular letter you have
就像有一封普通信件一样
a payload right that's the content and
内容的有效负载权
then you have some additional
那你还有一些额外的
information like properties headers
诸如属性标题之类的信息
address information and so on and so
地址信息等等
forth so and in spring events are
如此，春季事件是
represented generally as messages
一般表示为消息
message is as you can see it's a very
正如您所看到的，这是一个非常
simple structure basically it's a tuple
简单的结构基本上是一个元组
two so to speak right but it's through
可以这么说两个，但这是通过
the more structured where you have
您所在的地方越有条理
payload which is literally an object
有效载荷实际上是一个对象
could be anything and then you have a
可以是任何东西，然后你有一个
map of headers which is basically the
标头地图，基本上是
matter information that you want to
您想要的物质信息
transmit with your payload and we're
用您的有效载荷传输，我们
going to see it later on in action so
稍后再来看它，所以
let's start writing some code and and
让我们开始编写一些代码，然后
again I haven't really got into sprinkle
再一次我没有真正投入
extreme yet but I kind of want to show
极端但我想展示
you a little bit and then start talking
你一点点，然后开始说话
about some of the details so before I
关于一些细节，所以在我之前
even go how many of you are using spring
甚至去你们当中有多少人正在使用弹簧
cloud stream or familiar with spring
云流或熟悉春天
cloud stream okay
云流还可以
fair share and what's the fair share of
公平份额和什么是公平份额
people who don't know so which is good
不知道的人哪个好
so those for those of you guys who are
所以那些适合你们的人
using it what I'm going to show right
使用它，我将显示正确的内容
now it's probably going to be very
现在可能会非常
boring because you already seen it or
很无聊，因为您已经看过，或者
you already used it actually bad for
您已经使用它实际上不利于
those of you who didn't well welcome
那些不受欢迎的人
so what what I did is basically this is
所以我所做的基本上是
a blank sheet of paper
一张空白的纸
there is nothing disregard this person
没有人不理会这个人
class this is just a poacher that I'm
这只是我的偷猎者
going to use later right just to save
稍后使用只是为了保存
time and what you see is just a plain
时间，你所看到的只是一个平原
vanilla spring good application that
香草弹簧的好应用
there's absolutely nothing right so what
绝对没有对的东西怎么办
we want to do is we want to be able to
我们想要做的是我们想要能够
do something right and we want to be
做正确的事，我们希望成为
able to do something based on arrival of
能够根据……的到来做某事
the
的
- I'm kind of setting the Usk is based
-我有点想说Usk是基于
on the rival of the message - RabbitMQ
在邮件的竞争对手上-RabbitMQ
and for this case right could be Kafka
在这种情况下，可能是卡夫卡
could be anything so we have binders
可以是任何东西，所以我们有活页夹
which we'll talk about later but in this
稍后我们将讨论
case I'm gonna be using rabbitmq okay so
情况下我要用Rabbitmq好吧
I want to be able to send message to
我希望能够向发送消息
RabbitMQ and I want to be able to
RabbitMQ和我希望能够
somehow this message be transmitted to
该消息以某种方式被发送到
and result in invocation of my code now
并立即调用我的代码
think about in a good old days what
想想过去的美好时光
would you have to do to do that right
你需要做正确的事吗
configure connection factory session
配置连接工厂会话
factory all kinds of different things
工厂各种不同的东西
come message converters and so on and so
消息转换器等等
forth right so what I'm gonna do is I'm
正确，所以我要做的是
just going to write simple method
只是要写简单的方法
so I'll explain in a second what I'm
所以我待会再解释
doing
在做
so what I did I've written a very simple
所以我写的很简单
rudimentary spring closed application
基本的春季封闭申请
which which was gonna receive a piece of
那会收到一块
data and it's going to in this case the
数据，在这种情况下
piece of data is going to be a string is
一条数据将是一个字符串是
going to uppercase it right so as you
将其大写正确，以便您
can see at this point of time there is
可以看到在这个时间点
absolutely no wait for you to tell that
绝对不用等你说
this is going to be an application
这将是一个应用程序
that's going to receive a message from
将会收到来自的消息
rabbitmq that is what's going to come
即将发生的rabbitmq
from the binders which I'm going to talk
从我要说的活页夹中
about in a few minutes right so I'm
大约几分钟后，所以我
gonna start it so I thought what I
要开始了，所以我以为我
wanted to do come on stop
想停下来
so I'm going to start it and it started
所以我要开始了，它开始了
successfully and I'm going to go to my
成功，我要去我的
RabbitMQ console and you can see there's
RabbitMQ控制台，您可以看到
a Barcelona Barcelona group queue now
巴塞罗那巴塞罗那小组现在排队
let me quickly tell you why so basically
让我快速告诉你为什么如此
what I want to show you is is that this
我想告诉你的是
is really all you need to do to make
确实是您要做的一切
things work but I did one additional
一切正常，但我又做了一个
thing is which is I defined that for my
我为我定义的是
input destination and group I decided to
我决定输入的目的地和组
find the explicit names why I did that
找到我为什么这样做的明确名称
it's better for the demos because if I
这对演示更好，因为如果我
didn't do that
没有那样做
it would create an anima skew which
它将创建一个动画倾斜
means every time I restart the
表示每次我重新启动
application it would change right so for
应用程序将正确更改，因此
development you rarely have to do that
开发，您几乎不必这样做
big in fact for development you don't
实际上对于您来说发展并不重要
want to do it because you don't want to
想要这样做，因为你不想
worry about cleaning up the queues and
担心清理队列，
purging and so on and so forth like but
清除等等，诸如此类
for for demos or for real-life
用于演示或现实生活
applications you probably want to be
您可能想要成为的应用程序
able to have something like this right
能够拥有这样的权利
so but that's like I said it's about
所以但这就像我说的那样
many more that you would have to do so
您还需要这样做
now we have application started and I'm
现在我们已经开始申请了
gonna go to Barcelona queue and I'm just
要去巴塞罗那排队，我只是
gonna say hello
要打招呼
bricil ona write and send the message
Bricil Ona编写并发送消息
and we received
我们收到了
hello Barcelona and I can also actually
你好巴塞罗那，我也可以
go into so the message came in and the
进入这样的消息来了，
binders did all the work that I'm about
粘合剂完成了我要做的所有工作
to explain how everything works right
解释一切正常
and on basically invoked my method right
并基本上调用了我的方法
and then once I return the output the
然后一旦我返回输出
output pause again went to the binder
输出暂停再次转到活页夹
who was part of my application and was
谁是我申请的一部分
sent to the output queue which is
发送到输出队列
eventually the output Channel which
最终输出通道
eventually went to the output exchange
最终去了输出交流
which is bound to this output queue
绑定到此输出队列
which I did it manually and I can go and
我手动完成的，我可以去
say okay here we go here is here is my
说好，我们去这里，这是我的
caliber cilona uppercase right so you
口径cilona大写正确，所以你
guys familiar with rabbitmq for those
那些熟悉rabbitmq的人
who don't so the way RabbitMQ works is
谁不喜欢RabbitMQ的工作方式
that I'm sending you sending when you're
我正在发送给您，当您
sending a message you're sending it to
发送您要发送给的消息
the exchange arrival queue is a
交换到达队列是
messaging system that has internal
具有内部消息传递系统
routing you send a message to the
路由您发送一条消息到
exchange within the exchange it routes
在其路由交换内交换
the particular queue based on the
基于的特定队列
instructions in my case in
在我的情况下的说明
the instructions send it to just that
指令将其发送到
cue right so and then when you so that's
提示正确，然后当您提示时
how the message ended up in my method
消息如何以我的方法结束
then when I the result was went through
然后当我结果通过
the same process it was sent to the
它被发送到相同的过程
exchange by the name it was sent to the
交换的名称被发送到
exchange by the name output which as you
通过名称输出交换您
can see bound to the out queue and
可以看到绑定到出队列，并且
that's how we saw the message in the out
这就是我们看到信息的方式
queue so that's really the full circle
排队，这真的是一个完整的圈子
okay so now a couple of interesting sort
好吧，现在有几个有趣的问题
of features so obviously I didn't have
的功能，所以很明显我没有
to do anything I just wrote an
做任何我刚刚写的
application wrote a simple code and
应用程序编写了一个简单的代码，
simply by doesn't just start showing you
只是不只是开始向您展示
things so again we're living in the
事情再次如此，我们生活在
world of spring boots so now we're kind
spring boot 的世界，所以现在我们很友善
of managing dependency and and things
依赖和事物的管理
via Auto configuration so dependency by
通过自动配置，因此通过
pump right or by Gradle build so it's
正确地泵送或通过Gradle构建，因此
the fact that I included spring cloud
我包括春天云的事实
stream rabid binder into my palm this is
将狂热的粘合剂流到我的手掌中，这是
what made this thing work with RabbitMQ
是什么使RabbitMQ可以使用此功能
had I been using Kafka all I would need
如果我一直在使用Kafka，我会需要
to do no change of code no change of
不更改代码，不更改
properties all we need to do just change
属性，我们需要做的只是改变
this dependency from spring cloud stream
来自春天云流的这种依赖
binder rabbit or spring cloud stream
活页夹兔子或春天的云流
binder Kafka and we have a bunch of
活页夹卡夫卡，我们有一堆
different binders and in fact I'm kind
不同的粘合剂，实际上我很友善
of jumping ahead we are right now
前进，我们现在
formalizing the actual binding framework
规范实际的约束框架
because we just realized there was an
因为我们刚刚意识到有一个
interest in the community to develop
对社区发展的兴趣
other binders for other messaging and
其他消息传递的其他活页夹和
non messaging middlewares so so that's
非消息传递中间件，所以
really the kind of the gist of it now
真的是现在的要旨
this is so far a kind of a simple
到目前为止，这是一种简单的方法
application but what if I wanted to do
申请但我想怎么办
something more complex what if I want to
更复杂的事情，如果我想
receive that guy person well actually
实际上很好地接受那个家伙
before we go that there I'm gonna say I
在我们去那之前，我要说我
want to receive a message right because
想要正确接收消息，因为
what happens when you receive the
当您收到
message from spring clouds from from
来自Spring Cloud的消息来自
RabbitMQ internally within a bandit
土匪内部的RabbitMQ
represented as a message the fact that
表示为以下事实：
my method signature define is string
我的方法签名定义是字符串
that's the internal that's the beauty of
那是内部，那是美丽
the framework we by convention recognize
我们按照惯例认识的框架
that you really don't want the message
你真的不想要消息
you want the payload of the message so
你想要消息的有效载荷
there's a convention
有一个约定
they're saying that if you declare some
他们说，如果你宣布一些
kind of a poacher then we're going to
一种偷猎者，那么我们要
assume it is it is the payload of that
假设它是那个的有效载荷
message but if you want to receive if
消息，但如果您想接收
you want to receive the entire message
您想接收整个消息
then you can declare and because you for
那么你可以声明，因为你
example you may be interested in
您可能感兴趣的示例
metadata of some type right then you can
某种类型的元数据就可以了
say value that in this case get payload
说出在这种情况下获得有效载荷的值
that to upper case but message okay so
大写，但消息还可以
now I'm going to restart it
现在我要重启它
and you can see in the console that we
您可以在控制台中看到
receive the entire message so now you
收到整个邮件，所以现在您
can see the payload hello but you can
可以看到有效载荷你好，但是你可以
also see all kinds of relevant
也看到各种相关的
information especially when it comes to
信息，尤其是涉及到
working from like the the channels means
像渠道一样工作
rabbitmq properties and so on and so
rabbitmq属性等等
forth right so now again if I wanted to
现在再说一次，如果我想
say listen I don't want message I want
说听我不想留言
to receive a person I want to be able to
接待一个我想要的人
deal with the domain-specific objects
处理特定于域的对象
and I want you to worry about some type
我要你担心某种类型
of conversion I can do that to my person
我可以对我的人做到这一点
has a name attribute right so what I'm
有一个名字属性，所以我
gonna do I'm going to restart it again
我要重新启动一次
right but now I have to represent it as
对，但现在我必须将其表示为
a person so obviously I'm going to send
一个人，显然我要送人
a JSON string and it has to be you know
JSON字符串，必须是您知道的
something that
一些东西
so I received a person right so all of a
所以我收到了一个正确的人，所以
sudden it really as you can see if what
突然之间，如您所见，
I'm sort of hoping that you are able to
我有点希望你能够
observe is that you only worry about the
观察到您只担心
functional aspects of it will take care
它的功能方面会照顾
of the rest of it now when it comes to
现在谈到它的其余部分
the conversion with what you just
您所进行的转换
observe that happens based on the fact
观察事实发生
that we included about seven message
我们包含了大约七个消息
converters that we believe and based on
我们相信并基于
the feedback from the community are most
来自社区的反馈最多
relevant yes you can have a case where
相关是的你可以有一个案例
none of our message kind of errors we'll
我们所有的消息都不会出错
be able to handle that okay guess what
能够处理好吧，猜猜是什么
there is again if you go through the
如果您经历了
documentation and we actually revamped
文档，我们实际上进行了修改
our documentation we have a very kind of
我们的文档中
a nice sort of a looking field and a lot
很好看的领域，还有很多
of different formations but if you go to
不同的形式，但如果你去
formation there is a stream message
队中有一条流消息
converter you can define your own being
转换器，您可以定义自己的存在
put in your configuration and it will be
放入您的配置，它将是
added as the first one so you will get
添加为第一个，这样您将获得
the first crack at converting something
转换东西的第一个裂缝
so if if basically for 90% of the cases
所以如果基本上在90％的情况下
you can rely on message converters
您可以依靠消息转换器
provided by ask but for other cases you
由Ask提供，但在其他情况下，您
can simply extend the framework by
可以简单地通过扩展框架
providing your own message converter and
提供您自己的消息转换器，以及
so on all right back to this slides
所以就回到这张幻灯片
there's only a few more so and then
如此之多，然后
we're gonna get to the really cool stuff
我们将要去真正酷的东西
so spring integration I mentioned
所以我提到春天整合
earlier so to me it's kind of a very
较早所以对我来说这是一个非常
sort of a nostalgic and very relevant
有点怀旧和非常相关
topic to this day because look why do
今天的话题，因为看看为什么
you like when I talk about sprinkler
当我谈论喷头时，你喜欢
stream applications okay so you've
流应用程序好，所以您已经
developed an application how does it
开发了一个应用程序
really live in the real world well you
真正生活在现实世界中
don't have a single application you
您没有一个应用程序
rarely have a single application you
很少有一个应用程序
have multiple applications that are
有多个应用程序
connected via messaging middleware so
通过消息传递中间件连接，因此
you have some process here then there is
你在这里有一些过程，然后有
some kind of a messaging middleware in
某种消息传递中间件
the middle then another process and
中间然后另一个过程
another mystery much the middleware in
中间件中的另一个谜
the middle so you're essentially
中间，所以你本质上是
building the flows right and that's
建立正确的流程，那就是
really what spring integration allow us
真正的 Spring Integration 让我们
to do is basically implementation of
要做的基本上是执行
enterprise integration part patterns
企业集成部分模式
everybody read that book or know that
每个人都读那本书或知道
book or it's a very good book I will
书，或者我会写的很好
definitely recommend it it basically
绝对推荐它
outlines variety of different enterprise
概述各种不同的企业
integration patterns that kind of
那种整合模式
it's things in perspective so now when
这是观点，所以现在
you look at the code or discuss
你看代码或讨论
something with your colleague you really
和你的同事一起，你真的
have almost like a different lingo you
几乎像你一样的行话
say well this is a filter or this is a
说好，这是一个过滤器，或者这是一个
transformer or this is a router or this
变压器或这是路由器或此
is this so there is a various different
这是一个不同的地方吗
patterns so a message actually one of
模式，因此消息实际上是
the patterns defined by enterprise
企业定义的模式
integration patterns so but the very
整合模式，但非常
core pattern called pipes and filters
核心模式称为管道和过滤器
which is really what I just described
这就是我刚才描述的
you have pipe which is the messaging
你有管道这是消息
middleware and you have a filter which
中间件，您有一个过滤器
is basically a process that does
基本上是一个过程
something and then sends it to another
东西，然后将其发送给另一个
pipe and process repeats repeats and
管道和过程重复重复
repeats and the beauty of it is
重复，它的美丽是
everything is decoupled your producers
一切都与您的生产者脱钩
and consumers don't really know about
消费者并不真正了解
one another unless you want them to know
除非你想让他们知道
about one another and you do communicate
关于彼此，你确实可以交流
information through meta information in
通过元信息获取信息
a message like headers so yeah the issue
像标题这样的消息，是的，问题
is spring integration is that it it's a
春天的整合是
framework that allows you to configure
您可以配置的框架
flows within a single application
在单个应用程序中流动
context right
上下文权
so in other words you can do the same
所以换句话说，你可以做同样的事情
thing what I describe you but it's
我形容你的东西，但这是
within a single application context the
在单个应用程序上下文中
problem is Willy right now in the
问题是威利现在在
distributed world so we need a better
分散的世界，所以我们需要更好的
way of doing literally the same but in
字面上相同的方式，但
the distributed environment right so so
分布式环境就这样
sprinkler stream effectively takes
洒水流有效吸收
spring integration to the whole new
Spring Integration 到全新
level or takes the concept defined
级别或采用定义的概念
within enterprise integration patterns
企业整合模式内
and spring integration to the whole new
和 Spring Integration 到全新
level right so and in fact the binders
如此水平，实际上是粘合剂
and a lot of the internals of sprinkle
还有很多内部细节
out stream actually using spring
实际使用弹簧流出
integration as a library right because
集成为图书馆的权利，因为
there's a lot of code there that is
有很多代码是
reusable not just as a first-class
可重复使用，不只是一流
framework but also as a utility library
框架，但也作为实用程序库
that you can use when you're building
在构建时可以使用的
your own frameworks and one less thing
您自己的框架，少一件
just to underscore how much in love I am
只是为了强调我有多爱
with spring integration I usually when
与弹簧集成我通常在什么时候
I'm in the field or what I'm trying to
我在外地或正在尝试
prototype the requirement which ink
原型要求哪种墨水
which contains a some kind of a flow I
其中包含某种流程
start with spring integration I
从 Spring Integration 开始
literally map it with spring integration
用spring集成从字面上映射它
do you know why because I can actually
你知道为什么吗，因为我实际上可以
run it I can run the whole thing I can
运行它，我可以运行整个过程
implement my entire data flow my
实现我的整个数据流
enterprise try and trying to price data
企业尝试并尝试为数据定价
flow with just a single spring
只需一个弹簧即可流动
integration application context
集成应用程序上下文
and when I and that's what I did a
当我这样做的时候
couple times at the clients and want so
几次在客户那里，想要这样
in other words now they can not just
换句话说，现在他们不能只是
kind of draw diagrams and say that looks
一种绘制图，说看起来
fine they can actually envision what is
好的，他们实际上可以设想什么是
gonna happen how it's gonna happen you
将会发生怎么回事
know retry is routing you know
知道重试路由你知道
publish/subscribe and so on and so forth
发布/订阅等等
and then I say okay well now we can
然后我说好，现在我们可以
actually take that and extract these
实际采取并提取这些
pieces and each one of these boxes has
件，每个这些盒子都有
effectively become the single sprinkle
有效地成为单洒
out stream map and the pirates become
流出地图，海盗变成
remote messaging systems so highly
远程消息传递系统如此出色
recommend all right so sprinkle off
推荐没事，这样撒
stream so we kind of had a quick preview
流，所以我们有点快速预览
so what is it it's a framework to build
那么这是一个构建框架
highly scalable event-driven streaming
高度可扩展的事件驱动流
micro services right provides boot
微服务权提供启动
driven integration with message brokers
驱动与消息代理的集成
using destination binders so as I
使用目标资料夹
already mentioned the I would even
已经提到我什至
rephrase that spring cloud stream is
改写春天的云流是
really a binding framework because all
真正具有约束力的框架，因为所有
the internals that you've that in terms
您所拥有的内部条件
of passing messages and everything else
传递消息和其他所有信息
that's kind of done by utilizing spring
这是通过利用弹簧来完成的
integration and other spring messaging
集成和其他春季消息传递
libraries right so it leverages native
正确的库，因此可以利用本机
features of brokers while also providing
经纪人的功能，同时还提供
workarounds for not supported features
不支持的功能的解决方法
this is actually very important so for
这实际上非常重要，因此对于
example how many of you use Kafka okay
举例说明你们中有多少人使用Kafka
so Kafka great Kafka concept so you
所以卡夫卡伟大的卡夫卡概念，所以你
familiar with concept of a consumer
熟悉消费者的概念
groups and partitioning right so rabbit
组和分区的权利，所以兔子
doesn't provide that out of the box but
没有开箱即用，但
because rabbit provides internal routing
因为Rabbit提供了内部路由
features we were able to build consumer
我们能够建立消费者的功能
groups and partitioning inside of rabbit
兔子内部的分组和分区
in other words it's basically inside of
换句话说，它基本上在
a binder so we kind of emulated what
活页夹，所以我们有点模仿
Kafka does right so in other words
换句话说，卡夫卡是正确的
that's actually pretty cool because even
这实际上很酷，因为即使
though the that's what that's what
虽然那就是那
that's what really what I was trying to
那才是我真正想要的
say that even though the underlying
说，即使底层
messaging system does not provide that
邮件系统不提供
out of the box you can actually with a
开箱即用，您实际上可以
sprinkle out stream rabbit binder you
撒出流兔粘合剂你
actually have that feature so that's the
实际上具有该功能，因此
feature of the binder that built that
建立该活页夹的功能
build it internally based on some of the
在内部基于某些
functionality that was available in
可用的功能
underlying messaging framework in this
基础消息传递框架
case rabbitmq so and it honors
案例rabbitmq因此，它很荣幸
application configurations by the
应用程序配置
underlying frameworks I'm going to
我要去的基础框架
quickly switch
快速切换
- I'm not gonna run any code but for
-我不会运行任何代码，但是
example I use stream listener I'm just
例如我使用流监听器
precise what that last message means in
明确最后一条消息的含义
spring integration for those of you who
对于那些谁的春天整合
know there's another annotation called
知道还有一个叫做
that service activator or a transformer
该服务激活器或变压器
I could easily substitute this to add
我可以轻松地用它代替
service activator and everything will
服务激活器，一切都会
work the same way okay so I'm gonna do
以相同的方式工作好吧，我要去做
like at service activator and then
就像在服务激活器上一样
define input channel and output channel
定义输入通道和输出通道
and everything would be the same right
一切都会一样的
so in other words we honor if you we
换句话说，如果您
honor whatever frameworks that's that's
尊重那些就是这样的框架
internally we will honor those
在内部，我们将尊重那些
configurations and will boost rapid so
配置，并会迅速提升，
in other words if you migrating spring
换句话说，如果您要迁移春季
an integration application into spring
集成到Spring中的应用程序
cloud stream and you're not comfortable
云流，你不舒服
using two annotations you just want to
使用两个您只想要的注释
use one service activator because you're
使用一个服务激活器，因为您
familiar with it then go ahead use it
熟悉它然后继续使用它
okay
好的
few more slides so transparent content
几张幻灯片如此透明
and negotiations we already saw that
和谈判我们已经看到
ability to connect microservices to
将微服务连接到的能力
external system via binders we already
通过粘合剂的外部系统，我们已经
kind of touched on that flexible
那种灵活的感动
programming model this is what we're
编程模型，这就是我们
going to be talking right now for the
现在要为
rest of the presentation so build all
演示文稿的其余部分，请全部构建
and spring idioms and so on all right
春季习语等等
I kind of want to rush through it so
我有点想冲过去
it's a boot up as everything else in
它像其他所有东西一样启动
spring right now right you can use
现在就可以使用春天了
flexible configuration you can use I'm
可以使用的灵活配置
still mentioning XML because you know
仍然提到XML，因为您知道
what I'm still a fan of XML I don't care
我还是不喜欢XML的人
what anybody says things were but again
有人说什么，但又一次
you can what I'm trying to say is that
你可以我想说的是
you can we provided annotation
您可以提供注释
configuration we provide boot
我们提供的启动配置
configuration but we never really
配置，但我们从来没有真正
deprecated or moved away from XML so
不推荐使用或从XML移开，因此
whatever you only do whatever floats
不管你做什么浮标
your boat
你的船
so binders we have Kafka rabbit and then
所以粘合剂，我们有卡夫卡兔子，然后
a lot of community driven binders like
很多社区驱动的活页夹
Google a table yes as your soleus
谷歌一张桌子是你的比目鱼
there's a few other binders that I was
我还有其他一些活页夹
asked to review from Microsoft so
要求从Microsoft进行审查，因此
there's more binders coming on the
还有更多的活页夹
pipeline and we are actually planning
管道，我们实际上正在计划
right now in the early stages of our
现在在我们的早期阶段
sake binder
清酒粘结剂
which will give us the full reactive
这将使我们完全反应
back pressure support so on so and a
背压支撑等等
seamless integration because the
无缝集成，因为
beautification the seamless integration
美化无缝整合
with the rest of the spring stack like
其余的弹簧叠像
metrics Luth config circuit breaker
指标Luth配置断路器
whatever it is you wanted to use so this
无论您要使用什么，所以这
is really kind of the less slide this is
确实是这种较少的滑动
really what spring cloud stream is so
真的春天的云流是如此
you have at the very core is the
你最核心的是
destination binder so this nation binder
目的地活页夹，所以这个国家活页夹
is the wrapper into which you're gonna
是要包装的包装纸
slide your application right so you can
向右滑动您的应用程序，以便您可以
swap the binders that's at least the
交换至少是
idea kind of right once and then invoke
想法一次正确然后调用
it from anywhere type of thing right so
它可以从任何类型的事物中获取，所以
and then binders allow you to connect a
然后活页夹允许您连接一个
variety of different messaging systems
各种不同的消息传递系统
so again in this slide I'm kind of
所以再次在这张幻灯片中，我有点
showing you that you don't really have
告诉你你真的没有
to use single messaging system you can
使用单一消息系统，您可以
receive message from rabbit and send it
从兔子接收消息并发送
to Kafka or vice versa or use variety of
卡夫卡，反之亦然，或使用各种
different messaging systems
不同的消息传递系统
so that's really what spring cloud
所以这就是春天的云
stream is so let's go back to
流，所以让我们回到
programming model and claw I'm down the
编程模型和爪子我很失望
slide so let's get back into the code
滑动，让我们回到代码中
and start talking about what's new and
然后开始谈论新功能，
exciting so if you look at this
令人兴奋，所以如果你看看这个
application right doesn't it seem to be
申请权似乎不是
a bit verbose
有点冗长
I mean if you think about it I already
我的意思是，如果您考虑过，我已经
written I already told you that I
我已经告诉过你我
brought the binder into my palm as a
把活页夹带进了我的手掌
dependency and that enabled send and
依赖关系以及启用的发送和
receive messages right so why do I
正确接收消息，为什么我要
really need this why do I also need this
真的需要这个为什么我也需要这个
because effectively what I'm doing here
因为实际上我在这里做什么
if you look at what is the so this is an
如果你看看是什么，那么这是一个
able binding the processor is basically
能够绑定处理器基本上
a binding interface based on which we're
基于绑定接口
going to create a message channels right
将要创建一个消息通道
we're gonna create a proxy over them so
我们将为其创建代理，以便
they're our message channels so now all
他们是我们的信息渠道，所以现在所有
of a sudden you as a developer have to
突然之间，您作为开发人员必须
know about message channels so now as a
了解消息通道，现在作为
developer all of a sudden you exposed to
开发人员突然间暴露于
the fact that the message arriving from
消息来自的事实
RabbitMQ or Kafka is going to be sent to
RabbitMQ或Kafka将被发送到
message to the internal message channel
消息到内部消息通道
and at that point at that point of time
在那个时间点
spring integration is going to take over
Spring Integration 将接管
and invoke your message handler on your
并在您的计算机上调用您的消息处理程序
own only on your behalf right
只代表您自己拥有
why do you really need to know that let
你为什么真的需要知道让
me think about the overall overlay the
我考虑一下整体覆盖
lying story you want to write a function
你想写一个函数的撒谎故事
you write address the functional
你写地址功能
requirement and you want to be able to
要求，并且您希望能够
the framework take care of the rest you
框架会照顾您的其余部分
don't want to know about that internally
不想在内部知道
it deals with channels because in some
它处理渠道，因为在某些情况下
some binders they're not they're not
一些粘合剂，他们不是，他们不是
there's no channels like cause I poke a
没有类似的渠道，因为我戳了一个
stream binder binds you directly to the
流活页夹将您直接绑定到
message handler right so it's like to me
消息处理程序正确，对我来说就像
when I took over the framework it seemed
当我接管框架时
to be like it's a little bit too verbose
好像有点太冗长
a little too much information that you
太多的信息，你
that I as a developer would prefer not
我作为开发人员不愿意
to know so I decided I'm gonna remove
知道所以我决定我要删除
all that okay so we're gonna go back to
没关系，我们要回去
the blank sheet of paper and we're going
空白的纸，我们要去
to do this
去做这个
all right what do you see now
好吧，你现在看到了什么
that's dollar notation that is relevant
那是相关的美元符号
in spring right so what do you see now
春天来了，你现在看到了什么
is nothing more than a spring bootie
只不过是 spring boot
application with the beam of type
光束类型的应用
function okay now let's start it let's
功能正常，现在让我们开始吧，让我们
say with first
先说
and everything is working right so what
一切正常，那又怎样
do you think is this better than the
你认为这比
previous one I think it is right so so
上一个我认为是对的
what I'm kind of opening up to is the
我要开放的是
sprinklers function so a younger project
洒水装置的功能如此年轻
compared to sprinkle out stream it's
比起撒流
only about two years old maybe your and
只有大约两岁，也许你和
a half but what sprinkler function does
一半，但洒水功能做什么
is it basically brings java functions
它基本上带来了Java函数
into the spring ecosystem so as I'm
进入春季生态系统
gonna go along I'll you'll see some of
我会去的，你会看到一些
the kind of features of it but the point
它的特点，但重点
is that you can now represent your
是你现在可以代表你的
functional requirements using function
使用功能的功能需求
consumer or supplier or implement them
消费者或供应商或实施它们
and and we for example within sprinkler
并且我们例如在喷头内
extreme will effectively know what to do
极端会有效地知道该怎么办
now think about the amount of knowledge
现在想想知识量
that I was able to extract from it to
我能够从中提取到
avoid extra configuration you provided
避免您提供的额外配置
me with a single being of type function
有一个类型函数的我
okay fair enough which means I have no
好吧公平，这意味着我没有
conflict I know that within the concept
我知道在概念中存在冲突
of context of a sprinkler stream if I
如果我喷水流的上下文
see a function that must be a message
看到必须是消息的功能
handler kind of a duck typing right if
处理程序有点像鸭子，如果正确
it looks like a duck quacks like a duck
它看起来像鸭子，像鸭子一样嘎嘎叫
must be a duck right so the same thing
一定是鸭子，对吧，同样的事情
here so and because the function I know
这里是因为我知道的功能
it has input and output occurs I could
它有输入和输出发生我可以
also do the consumer which will be would
消费者也会做
be only input so this way I don't have
只能输入，这样我就没有了
to declare whether it's a processor
声明它是否是处理器
source or sink I can extract it just
源或汇，我可以将其提取出来
from the signature of your function okay
从你的功能签名好吗
and and basically I don't have to
而且基本上我不需要
provide any configuration okay so now
提供任何配置好吧，现在
the same thing will work if I do person
如果我做一个人，同样的事情会起作用
right I would have to do get name right
对，我必须要做正确的名字
so now I'm going to
所以现在我要
right so the same type conversion
对，所以相同类型的转换
everything works the same way now I'm
现在一切都以相同的方式进行
getting to the cool stuff what if I you
到酷的东西，如果我你呢
know it's just bull writing functions
知道这只是公牛的写作功能
how many of you are reactive people a
你们中有多少人是被动的
few okay
几行
so you probably prefer the right
所以你可能更喜欢正确的
function in a different way you probably
可能以不同的方式起作用
prefer to write it
喜欢写它
and then we have to change this
然后我们必须改变这个
right so now you can actually build the
对，所以现在您可以实际构建
internal reactive pipelines within
内部的内部反应管道
within the function itself so again I'm
在函数本身中，所以我再次
going to start it
要开始了
and everything works all right moving
一切正常
along so now I'm going to do another
所以现在我要去做另一个
function
功能
and it's also a beam okay now have two
现在也有两个光束
functions so now I have a conflict right
功能，所以现在我有冲突权
so I need to be able to somehow resolve
所以我需要能够以某种方式解决
this conflict but so what I do now I can
冲突，但是现在我可以做
specify in other words now I'm kind of
换句话说，我现在有点
following so I when I left spring boot
所以我离开 spring boot 时
didn't exist when I came back boot
当我重新启动时不存在
exists and I kind of decided to fully
存在，我决定完全
embrace it at least in my thought
至少在我的思想中拥抱它
process so I'm like I really want to
过程，所以我真的很想
only force you to configure something if
仅在以下情况下强迫您进行配置
you absolutely need to in this case we
在这种情况下，您绝对需要
have a tie you have two functions which
有一条领带，你有两个功能
one do you want to find two to the two
一个你想找到两个
the messaging system so you have your
邮件系统，让您拥有
gonna have to tell me so right now I'm
所以现在必须告诉我
gonna require you to provide a property
会要求您提供财产
so spring now why property why not
如此春天现在为什么财产为什么不
annotation because property while I'm
注解，因为我在置物
providing it through code you can
通过代码可以提供
provide it with the properties files
为它提供属性文件
right application that llamo or or
llamo或or的正确应用
whatever right or just from command
无论是正确的权利还是仅来自命令
lines so you can actually make it more
行，以便您实际上可以使它更多
dynamic spring cloud cloud stream stream
动态Spring Cloud云流
that function that finishin definition
完成定义的功能
people's upper case
人的大写
sprinkle on stream function definition
撒在流函数定义上
upper case ok so right now I said ok
大写还可以，所以现在我说还可以
well I have two functions there gonna be
好吧，我有两个功能
two beans loaded into function catalog
将两个bean装入功能目录
however when I send a message well I
但是，当我很好地发送信息时，
didn't put a system that out of print
并没有让系统绝版
lines so let's make sure I'm not lying
行，让我们确保我没有说谎
yet
然而
here's my hello okay so any questions so
这是我你好，所以有任何问题
far there's more okay so now here's
到目前为止，还可以，现在这里是
another sprinkler function okay so you
另一个洒水功能好，所以你
made a function out of a beam well I did
很好地发挥了功能
more what I can do now is one of the
我现在所能做的就是
benefit of sprinklers functional before
洒水喷头运行之前的好处
you even go there first of all what
你甚至首先去那里
allowed BOTS
允许的BOTS
functional programming or actually the
函数式编程或实际上
three interfaces function consumer and
三个接口分别作用于消费者和
supplier is because I always do this I
供应商是因为我总是这样做
always ask this question which is kind
总是问这个问题
of rhetoric rhetorical but makes you
修辞学的修辞学，却使你
think is there a requirement a business
认为有业务需要
requirement that you have dealt with
您已经处理的要求
dealing with or will be dealing with
处理或将要处理
that cannot be mapped to either supplier
无法映射到任何一个供应商
function or consumer think about it it's
功能或消费者考虑它的
like if we had these three interfaces
就像我们有这三个界面一样
back in early days of Java a lot of the
回到Java的早期
API is now would have been much simpler
API现在要简单得多
okay so but one of the features of Java
好的，但是Java的功能之一
functions is function composition right
功能是功能构成的权利
so we always take talk about how do we
所以我们总是谈论我们如何
you know how do you write our code with
你知道你怎么写我们的代码
the in terms of quality of code how many
在代码质量方面有多少
requirements is still little or just too
需求仍然很少或太少
big and so on and so forth let's say we
大等等等等，假设我们
finally come to conclusion well now you
终于得出结论，现在你
decided that I'm going to implement
决定我要实施
those requirements using functions but
使用功能的那些要求，但是
at least I implemented them those
至少我实现了那些
requirements are actually part of a
需求实际上是
bigger requirement right I remember like
我记得喜欢更大的要求
rod Johnson was always saying that there
罗德·约翰逊一直在说
is no such a thing as a complex problem
绝不是一个复杂的问题
every complex problem is just nothing
每个复杂的问题都没有
more than an array of simple problems
不仅仅是一系列简单的问题
right so the same thing here I mean you
是的，所以这里的意思是我
want to be able to look at your
希望能够看看你的
requirement
需求
break it apart by on very little pieces
通过很小的碎片将其分解
that are manageable that are
可管理的
understandable implemented as such
这样理解的实现
tested as such but then you want to
经过这样的测试，但然后您想
reassemble it back into one cohesive big
将其重新组装成一个有凝聚力的大块
requirement right so what I want to do
要求正确，所以我想做什么
here emulate this by simply saying I
这里简单地说我
want to be able to uppercase and then
希望能够大写，然后
echo right so
正确地回声
what I just did I've composed that's why
我刚刚完成的工作就是为什么
the property called not name but called
该属性不是名称，而是
definition because I can point to a name
定义，因为我可以指向一个名称
of a single function or can point to a
单一功能或可以指向
definition which is a composition
定义是组成
instruction to compose multiple
编写多个指令
functions into a message handler so in
功能进入消息处理程序，因此
this case we probably should be able to
这种情况下，我们应该应该能够
see the the value to be uppercase
看到值是大写的
because we first gonna invoke uppercase
因为我们首先要调用大写
then we're going to invoke echo right
然后我们要调用正确的回声
[Music]
[音乐]
yes yeah it because it's the same as to
是的，因为它与
the reason why I brought up functional
我提出功能的原因
composition is because in the pure Java
组成是因为在纯Java中
functions you can say function a and
您可以说功能a和
then function B and then function C
然后是功能B然后是功能C
that's exactly that's exactly what we're
那正是我们所要的
doing here so yes it is but it's good
在这里做，是的，但是很好
the question was for those of you who
问题是给那些谁
didn't hear will this pipe implies
没听见这个管道暗示
delegating back to rabbit and coming
委派回到兔子并来
back or is it internal just composition
返回还是内部公正的组成
that's internal composition that's the
那是内部的构成
answer
回答
so we basically composed a single
所以我们基本上组成了一个
function out of two functions
两个功能中的一个功能
and we got hello okay ten more minutes
我们打个招呼好十分钟
just enough time for the coolest feature
足够的时间来使用最酷的功能
so now these are the features that are
所以现在这些是
currently available and there is more
当前可用，还有更多
like I said I just you know 15 minutes
就像我说的，我只是你知道15分钟
is not enough I'm just kind of taking
我还不够
choose what I want to talk about but one
选择我想谈论的话题
of the new features that is already in
已有的新功能
the release and there is more
发布，还有更多
improvements that I actually done
我实际上所做的改进
yesterday routing so a lot of times like
昨天路由很多次
when it comes to sprinkle odd function
撒奇功能
you know well forget about function side
你很清楚忘记功能方面
specifically I'm going to talk about
我特别要谈论
sprinkler streams here so in this case I
喷头流在这里，所以在这种情况下，我
need to provide instructions to go here
需要提供说明以前往此处
there but let's pretend you have a use
在那里，但让我们假装你有用
case where based on the message you want
根据您想要的消息的情况
it to go to this handler or that handler
它去这个处理程序或那个处理程序
right so you want to be able to do some
对的，所以您希望能够做一些
kind of a routing so what you can do is
一种路由，所以您可以做的是
use the routing feature of functions
使用功能的路由功能
which is what it is is basically in
这基本上是什么
spring close function we've defined a
弹簧关闭功能，我们已经定义了
single function called a router right
单个功能称为路由器权
it's a well known name it's documented
这是一个众所周知的名字
and everything so all you need to do is
而所有您需要做的就是
for example there's couple of ways of
例如，有几种方法
enabling routers so what I'm going to do
启用路由器，所以我要做什么
it is to say spring cloud
就是说Spring Cloud
I just wanted to
我只是想
so what I'm gonna do here
所以我要在这里做什么
I said sprinkler function routing
我说喷水功能路由
enabled right so this function is not
正确启用，因此此功能不是
gonna be enabled by default is going to
默认情况下将启用
be enabled only if you provide an
仅在您提供
instruction because we don't want to
指导，因为我们不想
pollute environment or even in case if
污染环境，甚至万一
you decide to create your own functional
您决定创建自己的功能
neighbor out or something like that so
邻居或类似的东西
in this case routing function will
在这种情况下，路由功能将
require an additional meta information
需要额外的元信息
that gives it will receive the message
给它它将收到消息
on your behalf and it says okay well who
代表你说的很好，谁
do I call
我打电话吗
so so in this case because we remember I
所以在这种情况下，因为我们记得我
had to constantly start and stop server
必须不断启动和停止服务器
every time I wanted to change something
每当我想改变一些东西
right in this case I'm gonna start it I
在这种情况下，我要开始
have two functions in my catalog right
我的目录中有两个功能
now and I'm gonna go here and now I need
现在，我要去这里，现在我需要
to provide additional information now
现在提供其他信息
again one of the features of the binder
再次是粘结剂的特征之一
is whatever the information like HTTP
是像HTTP这样的信息
headers or message headers from RabbitMQ
RabbitMQ的标题或消息标题
or message headers from Kafka topic
或来自Kafka主题的邮件标题
they're going to be translated to
他们将被翻译成
message headers within the internal
内部邮件头
message representation so that's again
消息表示，这又是
something we do for you so basically
我们为您做的事情基本上
what I can do is I can say function that
我能做的是说功能
name I got it likewise it function name
我也知道它的名字函数名称
is gonna be echo and content type is
将是回声和内容类型是
going to be to explain write function
将要解释写功能
okay
好的
we got hello right
我们打对了
and if I wanted to do uppercase or upper
如果我想做大写或大写
upper case right
大写右
Barcelona obviously we're not gonna see
巴塞罗那显然我们不会看到
it in a council but we can go because of
它在议会中，但我们可以因为
how we implemented it but I can go to
我们如何实现它，但我可以去
output queue and and here's the
输出队列，这是
Barcelona right so all of a sudden I was
巴塞罗那吧，突然之间我是
able to so now you can imagine you can
能够这样，现在您可以想象可以
be sending messages and somewhere in the
正在发送消息，并且在
upstream is going to inject a header a
上游将注入一个标题
call saying book this function or
呼叫说书功能或
whatever and what we're working on which
无论我们在做什么
most likely you're not going to have to
最有可能您将不必
do because what we're working on is
这样做是因为我们正在努力的是
ability to provide an expression which
提供表达的能力
will evaluate any header and based on
将评估任何标头，并基于
that so in other words you can have some
也就是说，您可以拥有一些
native message coming in and based on
本机消息传入并基于
some value like accounts or whatever you
一些值，例如帐户或其他任何值
can route the specific function you know
可以路由您知道的特定功能
using an expression okay now again going
使用表达式好吧，现在再次
back to the whole spring boot mentality
回到整个春季引导心态
where you don't want to configure unless
除非您不想在哪里进行配置
you absolutely have to write so
你绝对要这样写
obviously in this case I have two
显然在这种情况下，我有两个
functions in other words so what so in
换句话说，功能如何
this case I have two functions and I
这种情况下，我有两个功能，我
enable routing another way of enable
启用路由另一种启用方式
routing is basically go back to using
路由基本上是回到使用
spring cloud stream that function that
春天的云流功能
definition equals router right so you
定义等于路由器正确，所以您
effectively enabled router by saying
通过说有效地启用路由器
okay well I'm gonna use the router as a
好吧，我要使用路由器作为
function so it is two ways of enabling
功能，这是启用的两种方式
it the reason why this is important is
它之所以重要的原因是
because what if you want to be able to
因为如果您希望能够
route to something and then the result
路由到某个东西，然后结果
of it has to be piped into something
它必须被输送到某些东西
else right so that's kind of a cool
否则对，这有点酷
thing to do so again so we're gonna I'm
再次这样做，所以我们要
gonna route we're gonna invoke let's say
我们要调用的路线
uppercase and then we're going to do the
大写，然后我们将要做
echo
回声
so i guess what i'm what i hope you're
所以我想我就是我希望你
observing is that you can build now very
观察到您现在可以建立
complex pipelines within sprinkle out
复杂的管道内散布
stream by simply addressing manageable
通过简单地解决可管理流
requirements of a manageable size and
规模可控的要求，以及
then compose them route them and so on
然后组成它们，路由它们，依此类推
and so forth so we started now we're
等等，所以我们现在开始
gonna go back to queue and i'm going to
要去排队，我要去
say the same thing so we're gonna do
说同样的话，我们要做
function dot name equals uppercase we're
函数点名称等于大写
route to uppercase and then content type
路由到大写，然后内容类型
to explain and then it's gonna echo
解释，然后回声
hello barcelona okay
你好巴塞罗那好吗
one last demo is what if you like I was
最后一个演示是如果您喜欢我的话
saying that's you know somewhere in the
说那是你知道的
pipeline you want to be able to have a
您希望能够拥有的管道
function that will actually because you
该功能实际上是因为您
may not be able to know which function
可能无法知道哪个功能
do you want to invoke but there is a
你想调用但有一个
function upstream or somewhere within
在上游或内部某处起作用
one of your functions I'm sorry one of
您的一项功能，对不起其中一项
your function will know based on some
您的功能将基于一些
information internally which method to
内部信息使用哪种方法
invoke so I'm gonna call it in rich or
调用，这样我就可以称之为丰富或
function so let's let me write it real
功能，所以让我写它真实
quick so and it's going to be message
这么快，这将是消息
and what we're going to do is we're
而我们要做的是
going to say okay I'm going to say
会说好吧我会说
builder that with payload value that set
用有效载荷值设置的构建器
header
标头
Oh
哦
okay so basically we have a function
好的，所以基本上我们有一个功能
called enriched so what I'm gonna do is
叫做丰富，所以我要做的是
I'm good thank you
我很好谢谢
so I'm gonna do the enrich so we're
所以我要做丰富的，所以我们
gonna call the we're gonna call call the
会打电话给我们
function basically create the pipeline
功能基本上创建管道
where we're gonna this so when I invoke
我们要去哪里，所以当我调用
when I send the message is gonna it
当我发送邮件时
created this one big function where the
创建了这一大功能，
first function is going to be invoke is
第一个要被调用的功能是
in rich function then obviously at that
在丰富的功能，然后显然在
point of time it's gonna inject the
时间点它会注入
header knowing which route it's going to
标头知道它要去哪条路线
send to the router function which
发送到路由器功能
already going to have the header and
已经要有标题和
it's going to go into the echo and
它会进入回声，
and we got it okay so guys it's 9:50
而且我们还好，所以是9:50
thank you very much I'll be out here for
非常感谢你，我会在这里
any questions what I would also
任何问题我也要
recommend like I said yaku is presenting
像我说的yaku推荐一样推荐
next he is a got really cool demos in a
接下来他是一个非常酷的演示
really cool content so thank you very
非常酷的内容，非常感谢
much for attending
很多参加
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]